[{"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm eleven. How old are you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What happens if you do not find a host for this Goa'uld", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "If the Goa'uld dies, then you will die as well", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Okay, that's the converter, right", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What? W.. When did we talk about the heating element", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't draw", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Draw me your reactor core. Give me an idea of what it looks like", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You don't draw? Everyone draws", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't draw", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. It is not something I am required to do. I've never had to draw before", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Perhaps it would be better for my friend to return", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend is already familiar with the subject", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He stays here with the other past Urrone", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What is play", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "There is no need for concern. These children are well cared for", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "My son is here now", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It is most certainly in her best interest", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "We do not harm our children, Dr my friend. You have seen my friend, you have seen how well he is cared for", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Please return me to my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't need your help", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You claim to love knowledge, yet when you find something you don't like, you demand that we change to please you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "There is no better way than the Averium", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "And you never once thought otherwise", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "And what if my friend does", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes. Look, you came here to learn, right? There's something I have to show you, but I have to take you off the base for it", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No. I don't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Of course it is", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh yeah. It's way more than right", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Thank you Colonel my friend, for teaching this to me", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Learning-Curve.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I have a duty to my people. My knowledge is important to them. You did promise", "qsentId": 32}]